{
	"records":[
		{
			"question":"160 ÷ 2 =",
			"answer":80
		},
		{
			"question":"500 x 5 =",
			"answer":2500
		},
		{
			"question":"420 ÷ 60 =",
			"answer":7
		},
		{
			"question":"800 x 5 =",
			"answer":4000
		},
		{
			"question":"720 ÷ 9 =",
			"answer":80
		},
		{
			"question":"90 ÷ 30 =",
			"answer":3
		},
		{
			"question":"120 ÷ 30 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"80 x 40 =",
			"answer":3200
		},
		{
			"question":"1000 ÷ 20 =",
			"answer":50
		},
		{
			"question":"108 ÷ 9 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"240 ÷ 60 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"90 x 400 =",
			"answer":36000
		},
		{
			"question":"500 x 6 =",
			"answer":30000
		},
		{
			"question":"350 ÷ 50 =",
			"answer":7
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 700 =",
			"answer":3500
		},
		{
			"question":"80 x 30 =",
			"answer":2400
		},
		{
			"question":"900 x 2 =",
			"answer":1800
		},
		{
			"question":"640 ÷ 8 =",
			"answer":80
		},
		{
			"question":"400 x 7 =",
			"answer":2800
		},
		{
			"question":"320 ÷ 80 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"20 x 500 =",
			"answer":10000
		},
		{
			"question":"3600 ÷ 12 =",
			"answer":300
		},
		{
			"question":"960 ÷ 80 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"490 ÷ 7 =",
			"answer":70
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 600 =",
			"answer":3600
		},
		{
			"question":"360 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":60
		},
		{
			"question":"1000 ÷ 10 =",
			"answer":100
		},
		{
			"question":"400 x 4 =",
			"answer":1600
		},
		{
			"question":"2800 ÷ 7 =",
			"answer":400
		},
		{
			"question":"80 x 100 =",
			"answer":8000
		},
		{
			"question":"840 ÷ 120 =",
			"answer":7
		},
		{
			"question":"42 ÷ 7 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"5400 ÷ 90 =",
			"answer":60
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 12000 =",
			"answer":24000
		},
		{
			"question":"2500 ÷ 5 =",
			"answer":500
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 1000 =",
			"answer":8000
		},
		{
			"question":"120 x 9 =",
			"answer":1080
		},
		{
			"question":"50 x 80 =",
			"answer":4000
		},
		{
			"question":"180 ÷ 30 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"400 x 30 =",
			"answer":12000
		},
		{
			"question":"900 x 7 =",
			"answer":6300
		},
		{
			"question":"80 x 90 =",
			"answer":7200
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 400 =",
			"answer":3600
		},
		{
			"question":"60 x 500 =",
			"answer":9000
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 600 =",
			"answer":4200
		},
		{
			"question":"80 x 20 =",
			"answer":1600
		},
		{
			"question":"400 ÷ 5 =",
			"answer":80
		},
		{
			"question":"320 ÷ 40 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"400 x 9 =",
			"answer":3600
		},
		{
			"question":"80 x 40 =",
			"answer":3200
		},
		{
			"question":"70 x 8 =",
			"answer":560
		},
		{
			"question":"1200 x 4 =",
			"answer":4800
		},
		{
			"question":"110 x 6 =",
			"answer":660
		},
		{
			"question":"480 ÷ 60 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"300 x 9 =",
			"answer":2700
		},
		{
			"question":"80 x 80 =",
			"answer":6400
		},
		{
			"question":"600 ÷ 3 =",
			"answer":200
		},
		{
			"question":"400 x 9 =",
			"answer":3600
		},
		{
			"question":"2700 ÷ 3 =",
			"answer":900
		},
		{
			"question":"600 x 40 =",
			"answer":24000
		},
		{
			"question":"500 x 8 =",
			"answer":4000
		},
		{
			"question":"9000 x 5 =",
			"answer":45000
		},
		{
			"question":"600 x 12 =",
			"answer":7200
		},
		{
			"question":"12 x 90 =",
			"answer":1080
		},
		{
			"question":"8000 ÷ 2 =",
			"answer":4000
		},
		{
			"question":"350 ÷ 5 =",
			"answer":70
		},
		{
			"question":"640 ÷ 8 =",
			"answer":80
		},
		{
			"question":"90 x 30 =",
			"answer":2700
		},
		{
			"question":"200 x 90 =",
			"answer":18000
		},
		{
			"question":"60 x 30 =",
			"answer":1800
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 4 =",
			"answer":28
		},
		{
			"question":"900 ÷ 9 =",
			"answer":100
		},
		{
			"question":"56 ÷ 7 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"700 x 3 =",
			"answer":2100
		},
		{
			"question":"100 ÷ 50 =",
			"answer":2
		},
		{
			"question":"440 ÷ 4 =",
			"answer":110
		},
		{
			"question":"800 x 9 =",
			"answer":7200
		},
		{
			"question":"1200 x 2 =",
			"answer":2400
		},
		{
			"question":"360 ÷ 9 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"300 x 3 =",
			"answer":900
		},
		{
			"question":"700 x 6 =",
			"answer":4200
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 9000 =",
			"answer":36000
		},
		{
			"question":"800 x 2 =",
			"answer":1600
		},
		{
			"question":"1800 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":300
		},
		{
			"question":"4000 x 1 =",
			"answer":4000
		},
		{
			"question":"70 ÷ 7 =",
			"answer":10
		},
		{
			"question":"30 x 8 =",
			"answer":240
		},
		{
			"question":"900 x 5 =",
			"answer":4500
		},
		{
			"question":"60 x 7 =",
			"answer":420
		},
		{
			"question":"700 x 9 =",
			"answer":6300
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 500 =",
			"answer":4500
		},
		{
			"question":"40 x 6 =",
			"answer":240
		},
		{
			"question":"90 x 8 =",
			"answer":720
		},
		{
			"question":"300 x 8 =",
			"answer":2400
		},
		{
			"question":"120 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":20
		},
		{
			"question":"96 ÷ 8 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"70 x 50 =",
			"answer":3500
		},
		{
			"question":"6300 ÷ 7 =",
			"answer":900
		},
		{
			"question":"72 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"72 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":12
		}
	]
}
